{"quizName":"ERP Chapter 4","questions":[{"question":"Which one of the following is not a type of organizational data that is utilized in the procurement process?","options":["Client","Company Code","Storage Location","Purchasing Organization","Manufacturing Plant"],"answerIndex":4},{"question":"What is a storage location? ","options":["The place where raw materials are received","The place within a plant where materials are kept until they are needed","The place where materials are collected for staging and inspection","The place within a plant where machines are installed for production purposes","The place within a plant where finished goods are kept for sale"],"answerIndex":1},{"question":"Which organizational element(s) control(s) the entry of accounting data in the vendor master?","options":["Purchasing organization","Client","Company Code","Client and Company Code","Client and Purchasing Organization"],"answerIndex":3},{"question":"A purchasing organization is involved in all of the following operations except","options":["Negotiating contracts and agreements","Negotiating pricing with vendors","Evaluating and identifying vendors","Determining storage locations within the plant"],"answerIndex":3},{"question":"Which one of the following is not a model of the purchasing organization?","options":["Enterprise level","Company level","Client level","Plant level","Cross-plant"],"answerIndex":2},{"question":"Within the plant-level purchasing organization, also known as a plant-specific purchasing Organization,","options":["Each plant has its own purchasing organization","One purchasing organization is responsible for multiple plants","Only one purchasing organization for all plants","One purchasing organization is responsible for all company codes in the enterprise","Two or more purchasing organizations are responsible for each plant"],"answerIndex":0},{"question":"A purchasing group is an individual or a group of individuals who are responsible for all of the following except","options":["Creating purchase requisitions","Negotiating contracts and agreements","Requesting quotations from vendors","Creating and monitoring purchase orders","Planning for material requirements"],"answerIndex":1},{"question":"Which one of the following is not one of the data types that are relevant to the purchasing process? ","options":["Material master","Vendor master","Sales master","Purchasing info records","Conditions"],"answerIndex":2},{"question":"The key data in the purchasing view of the material master are ","options":["The purchasing organization, the goods receipt processing time, and the delivery tolerances","The purchasing group, the goods receipt processing time, and the delivery tolerances","The purchasing group, the invoice, and the delivery tolerances","The purchasing group, the material master, and the delivery tolerances","The price, the storage location, and the delivery date"],"answerIndex":1},{"question":"Data in the vendor master are grouped into which three segments? ","options":["General data, storage data, and purchasing data","General data, storage data, and inventory data","Storage data, accounting data, and purchasing data","Storage data, accounting data, and pricing data","General data, accounting data, and purchasing data"],"answerIndex":4},{"question":"General data in a vendor master contain all of the following except:","options":["Name","Address","Communication","Payment terms and methods","Search term"],"answerIndex":3},{"question":"Which of the following is an intersection or combination of material data and vendor data?","options":["Condition type","Purchasing info record","Stock transfer","Third-party order","Search term"],"answerIndex":1},{"question":"Which item category would you use to have your vendor ship goods directly to your customer?","options":["Consignment","Third-party","Stock transfer","Standard","Transfer posting"],"answerIndex":1},{"question":"Materials that are acquired to be used within the organization are referred to as","options":["Stock materials","Transfer materials","Vendor materials","Consumable materials","None of the above"],"answerIndex":3},{"question":"Which of the following account assignment categories is used when the company acquires a fixed asset?","options":["Cost center","Asset","Order","Sales order","Project"],"answerIndex":1},{"question":"Which of the following document types is not utilized during the Purchasing process?","options":["Material documents","Fl documents","CO documents","Picking document","Invoice"],"answerIndex":3},{"question":"A FI document includes a header and an items section.  Which of the following data are included in the items section?","options":["Document number","Account","Storage location","Document date","Document currency"],"answerIndex":1},{"question":"Which of the following statements about a plant is not true?","options":["A plant can be assigned to more than one company code","A company code can have more than one plant","A plant is a key organizational element in purchasing","A plant can be assigned to only one company code","A plant must have at least one storage area"],"answerIndex":0},{"question":"Which of the following goods movements need not involve a physical movement of materials?","options":["Goods receipt","Goods issue","Stock transfer","Transfer posting","None of the above (all involve physical movement of materials)"],"answerIndex":3},{"question":"Which element of the requirements determination process involves creating the requisition?","options":["Data","Task","Trigger","Outcomes","None of the above"],"answerIndex":1},{"question":"A company can use which of the following to select a vendor from a list of potential suppliers ?","options":["Source list","Company code","Vendor master","Material master","None of the above"],"answerIndex":0},{"question":"Which element of a purchase order includes communicating with the vendor?","options":["Trigger","Data","Task","Outcome","None of the above"],"answerIndex":3},{"question":"Which item is included in the header of a purchase order?","options":["Order quantity","Vendor","Delivery date","Price","None of the above"],"answerIndex":1},{"question":"SAP can utilize which of the following media to communicate with a vendor?","options":["Web services","EDI","Fax","Print","All of the above"],"answerIndex":4},{"question":"Which of the following is(are) a form of data within the goods receipt step?","options":["Material ordered","Quantity delivered","Verification","Storage location","All of the above"],"answerIndex":4},{"question":"Which of the following is a form of invoice verification?","options":["Three-way match","Quality management","Inspection lot","Warehouse management","None of the above"],"answerIndex":0},{"question":"Which element of the payment step includes selecting a bank?","options":["Trigger","Data","Outcome","Task","None of the above"],"answerIndex":3},{"question":"Which of the following facilitates the integration between vendor master data and financial accounting?","options":["Vendor account number","Reconciliation account","Accounts payable number","Material number","Accounts receivable number"],"answerIndex":1},{"question":"Purchasing information systems are a component of which system?","options":["Logistics information systems","Business intelligence systems","Financial information systems","Human resource information systems"],"answerIndex":0},{"question":"Storage locations are places within a plant were materials are kept until they are needed. ","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":0},{"question":"There can only be one storage location within a plant. ","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":1},{"question":"A storage location is a key organizational element in purchasing.","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":0},{"question":"A purchasing organization is involved only in negotiating prices with vendors ","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":1},{"question":"Typically, there are three models of purchasing organizations: enterprise-level, company-level, and plant-level. ","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":0},{"question":"The enterprise‐level purchasing organization is also known as the cross‐company code purchasing organization. ","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":0},{"question":"The company-level purchasing organization is the most centralized model.","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":1},{"question":"The enterprise-level purchasing organization is the most centralized model. ","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":0},{"question":"A plant can belong to more than one company code.","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":1},{"question":"The most decentralized model of purchasing organizations is the plant‐specific purchasing organization.","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":0},{"question":"A purchasing group is an internal group that is responsible for executing the procurement process.","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":1},{"question":"A purchasing organization is an individual or a group of individuals who are responsible for purchasing activities for a material or group of materials. ","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":1},{"question":"Vendor master data include the data needed to conduct business with a vendor and to execute transactions related to the procurement process.","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":0},{"question":"The method used to value material is defined in the material master.","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":0},{"question":"Different material types have different required material views.","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":0},{"question":"General data related to a vendor are accessible to all company codes in a client.","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":1},{"question":"Purchasing data related to a vendor are accessible to all purchasing organizations.","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":1},{"question":"Material master data can be defined differently for different organizational levels.","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":0},{"question":"A purchasing info record is an intersection or combination of material and accounting data.","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":1},{"question":"Accounting data related to a vendor are accessible to all clients in a company code.","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":1},{"question":"Item categories in a purchase order determine the process steps used to procure materials.","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":0},{"question":"Consumable materials are acquired to be used within an organization.","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":0},{"question":"When purchasing consumable materials, an account assignment category and specific account assignment objects must be provided when the purchase order is created.","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":0},{"question":"A goods movement is not required when changing the status of material from “in quality inspection” to “unrestricted use”.","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":1},{"question":"A plant-to-plant movement of goods does not generate an accounting document.","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":1},{"question":"A goods receipt cannot be accomplished without a movement type.","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":0},{"question":"A stock transfer does not involve a change in storage location.","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":1},{"question":"A transfer posting changes the stock status of a material and need not involve a physical movement of goods.","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":0},{"question":"A goods movement is a transaction that causes a change in stock value or status.","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":0},{"question":"Materials cannot be moved from one company code to another because each company code uses a different set of books.","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":1},{"question":"A transfer posting is used to move materials from one storage location to another.","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":1},{"question":"A transfer posting does not generate a material document.","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":1},{"question":"Requirements for materials must be created manually.","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":1},{"question":"The data needed to create a purchase requisition are the item category, quantity, desired delivery date, and desired delivery location or receiving plant. ","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":0},{"question":"A requisition represents a legal obligation to make the purchase.","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":1},{"question":"The header section of a purchase order contains information such as purchase order number, vendor, currency, dates, and payment terms.","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":0},{"question":"The primary task of the order processing step is to create and send the purchase order to the vendor.","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":0},{"question":"SAP cannot utilize any media except Web services to communicate a purchase order to a vendor.","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":1},{"question":"Materials ordered in multiple purchase orders must be delivered in multiple shipments.","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":1},{"question":"The material master is updated after the invoice verification step of the procurement process has been completed.","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":0},{"question":"The material master is updated after the goods receipt step of the procurement process has been completed.","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":0},{"question":"Tolerances for price variations among purchase orders, invoices, and goods receipts are allowed, but tolerances for quantity variances are not.","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":1},{"question":"Invoice verification authorizes payment of the invoice to the vendor.","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":0},{"question":"Payments must be made automatically through a payment program.","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":1},{"question":"Electronic payments are sent automatically.","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":0},{"question":"Work lists display lists of master data and documents that are generated during the execution of a process.","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":1}]}